Tianna Mosby

804-467-7533 | mosbyts@vcu.edu | LinkedIn | Portfolio | GitHub

SUMMARY

An energetic, enthusiastic and creative developer with experience in software engineering including programming, databasing, server management and more. Tremendously self-motivated and highly skilled with the desire to lead and support the development, implementation and maintenance of responsive websites and applications. Certified Full Stack Developer through the University of Richmond. Brings a digital communications perspective to web applications with demonstrated success in digital media platform management, content creation and advertising.

EDUCATION

University of Richmond | Richmond, VA Full Stack Web Developer Certification

P1 Learning, P1 Futures Program | Richmond, VA Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) Digital Media Sales Certification

Virginia Commonwealth University | Richmond, VA

Bachelor of Science in Mass Communications
Honors and Activities: Cum Laude, Dean's List, Vice President of Disney Appreciation Club

SKILLS

- JavaScript and ¡Query
- WordPress CMS
- Public Relations
- MySQL, Express and Mongo DB
- HTML, CSS and Bootstrap
- Adobe Systems and Microsoft Office
- React
- Cisco Meraki and Umbrella
- Salesforce and Bullhorn CRMs

EXPERIENCE

Henrico Too Smart 2 Start | Henrico, VA Social Media Coordinator | **02/2019-Present**

Increase community awareness on substance abuse through consistent voice and reliable presence on social media platforms. Act as communications manager in leading public relations team on developing and implementing social media campaigns. Design physical and digital creatives to be posted in local community spaces and on social media.

Astyra Corporation | Richmond, VA

Corporate Communications Specialist | 04/2019-Present

Develops and executes the company's branding campaigns through social media platforms, quarterly newsletters and employee outreach communications. Measures and reports on the effectiveness of said communications activities and use analytics to improve digital marketing strategy. Curates visual and written content that increases audience interaction and presence on company website, blog and social media pages through research and Search Engine Optimization (SEO) practices.

Provides in-person technical support for application, hardware, telephone and network-related issues. Manages the IT department's documentation, asset management and the development and implementation of policies, standards and processes. Acts as the manager for IT interns and entry-level employees and creates custom training plans.

Operations Admin and Executive Assistant | 04/2018-03/2019

PROJECTS

Bamazon Store

App Developer and Database Engineer

The Bamazon Store is the low-budget version of an Amazon-like storefront that is run in the user's terminal. In this app, the user can virtually purchase common items with real-time databasing used to update the products' quantities.

Created with:

- MySQL
- JavaScript/jQuery
- Inquirer (JSON package)
- Terminal (Git Bash)

Hitchhikers' Travel App

Web Developer and Debugger

This GitHub deployed web application helps users plan their future trip using a single website. Instead of browsing the web for local attractions, weather information, traffic alerts and crime rates, the user can find all this information at the one-stop-shop Hitchhikers' Travel App.

Created with:

- JavaScript/jQuery
- Various API's/AJAX calls
- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap
- AOS (Animate On Scroll)
- Animate.css